Finding Aid for Gary Muffly photographic negatives, 1931
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Gary Muffly photographic negatives 1931
Muffly, Gary
43 items in 1 folder
92585 UAs
Member of University of Michigan Class of 1932. Negatives made in spring and summer, 1931, by Gary Muffly; include University of Michigan campus and buildings, construction of the Law Building, tug-of-war, and other student activities.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of Gary Muffly (donor no. 6181 ) and came to the library in 1978.
The collection is open to research.
Gary Muffly was a graduate of the University of Michigan, class of 1932. During the spring and summer of 1931, he took many photographic images of campus buildings and student activities. Included are views of the construction of law school buildings, a student tug-o-war, and the games between the freshman and sophmore classes.
The Muffly collection consists of 43 photographic negatives (2 1/2 x 4 1/2") taken during the Spring and Summer of 1931.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Lawyers' Club (University of Michigan); University of Michigan--Buildings.; University of Michigan--Campus.; University of Michigan--Students--Social life and customs--1931-1940.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- Negatives, 43 photographic negatives in 1 folder (Folder UAs)
  - Law Building excavation, State Street-Trucks and steam shovels, Spring, 1931, na 4402
  - Law Building excavation-Steam shovel versus stump, Spring, 1931, na 4403
  - Naval Tank-Model tow vehicle and instrumentation, Spring, 1931, na 4404
  - Naval Tank models, Spring, 1931, na 4405
  - Engineering Arch and coed dress, Spring, 1931, na 4406
  - Law Building-Demolition and construction. Spring, 1931, na 4407
  - Law Building. Foundation concrete being poured, Spring, 1931, na 4408
  - Looking south down State St. from Union Tower, Spring, 1931, na 4408
    (Note: negative nos. 4408-4418 part of series entitled "Panorama from Union Tower")
  - Looking south by southeast from Union Tower. Law buildings and construction. Spring, 1931, na 4410
  - Looking southeast from Union Tower-Law buildings, Spring, 1931, na 4411
  - Looking east by southeast from Union Tower -- Law and architecture buildings, Spring, 1931, na 4412
  - Looking east from Union Tower-Engineering and law buildings, Spring, 1931, na 4413
  - Looking east by northeast from Union Tower-Unidentified building (Romance Language?),Spring, 1931, na 4414
  - Looking east by northeast from Union Tower Alumni Memorial Hall, Spring, 1931, na 4415
  - Looking northeast by north from Union Tower -- End of Angell Hall, etc., Spring, 1931, na, 4416
  - Looking north by north east from Union Tower, na 4417
  - Looking north from Union Tower. Spring, 1931, na 4418
  - Sophmore band and parade to Frosh-Soph. Tug-o-war, Spring, 1931, na 4419
  - Sophmores carry rope for tug-o-war, Spring, 1931, na 4420
  - Carrying rope across Huron River, Spring, 1931, na 4421
  - Carrying rope across Huron River, Spring, 1931, na 4422
  - Tug-o-war-rope on upswing, Spring, 1931, na 4423
  - Tug-o-war-rope on downswing, Spring, 1931, na 4424
  - Tug-o-war-Frosh(?) team pulling in rope, Spring, 1931, na 4425
  - Frosh-Soph Spring Games-pillow fight, Spring, 1931, na 4426
  - Frosh-Soph Spring Games-pillow fight. Spring, 1931, na 4427
  - Frosh-Soph Spring Games-obstacle race, Spring, 1931, na 4428
  - Frosh-Soph Spring Games-obstacle race, Spring, 1931, na 4429
  - Alumni Memorial Hall, Spring, 1931, na 4430
  - Law Building. Construction-concrete forms, May 27, 1931, na 4431
  - Michigan Union, June 9, 1931, na 4432
  - Back gate, President's residence, June 9, 1931, na 4433
  - Law Building entrance, June 9, 1931, na 4434
  - East Engineering Building, Summer, 1931, na 4435
  - Engineering Annex and clock, Summer, 1931, na 4436
  - League Building, Summer, 1931, na 4437
  - Law Building -- foundation, Summer, 1931, na 4438
  - Law Building-steel erection, Summer, 1931, na 4439
  - Law Quadrangle from Union Tower, Summer, 1931, na 4440
  - Law Quadrangle from Union Tower, Summer, 1931, na 4441
  - Law Quadrangle from Union Tower, Summer, 1931, na 4442
  - Angell Hall, Summer, 1931, na 4443
  - Law Club, inside portico, Summer, 1931, na 4444